adslivemedia.com 2014-06-29

# Privacy Policy | AdsLiveMedia

January 2013

ADS Live Media provides an online advertising sale and display service (the “Service”) for Internet website owners (“Publishers”). We enable advertisers to place advertisements via the Service on one or more sites belonging to Publishers. We enable our corporate customers (“Network Operators”) to create and manage networks of Publishers and Advertisers using tools we provide. The Service runs on software developed and hosted by ADS Live Media, its subsidiaries, and third-party contractors.

ADS Live Media recognizes the importance of information privacy. This Privacy Policy describes ADS Live Media’s practices for gathering, storing, using and disseminating information, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard that information. We may change this policy from time to time. All changes will be posted to this site, and you are encouraged to periodically check back to this site for any changes to the privacy policy.

A. INFORMATION COLLECTION

If you are a Publisher, Advertiser, or Network Operator, you can browse certain areas of the Service without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. For example, your user ID is displayed throughout the Service and is therefore available to our employees and contractors. If you choose to provide us with personal information, you consent to the transfer to and storage of that information on servers located in the United States.

If you are a Publisher, Advertiser, or Network Operator, ADS Live Media requires certain information related to your business, your website, and your use of the Service. ADS Live Media will collect and store this information. Cox Digital Solutions may collect your email addresses, mailing and billing address and order information, IP address, information about your site, including but not limited to your site’s page impressions, advertising prices, and information about your visitors.

To improve and personalize the Service, ADS Live Media may collect information about your business from third parties and provide this information on your behalf. This information may include, but is not limited to the following: third-party counts of monthly page views, visitor composition, and rankings in various indices. ADS Live Media may not provide you the option to turn off the presentation of this information.

ADS Live Media may collect tax information, including Value Added Tax (VAT) or federal tax ID numbers. ADS Live Media will collect information regarding your activities with respect to the Service. ADS Live Media will collect any comments you send to us and any information you post to the ADS Live Media site or on a Publisher site. ADS Live Media may also collect information through the use of Cookies (see below). ADS Live Media collects personal information when you: (1) register with ADS Live Media to become a Publisher, Advertiser, or Network Operator, (2) provide comments or submit a problem to ADS Live Media, (3) request information from ADS Live Media and provide your name or return contact information, or (4) respond to special offers, contests or surveys. As part of the registration process, you may be asked to provide contact information and other personally identifying information.

B. COOKIES

“Cookies” are small data files that may be downloaded to your computer when you visit the ADS Live Media site or a Publisher site and permit the ADS Live Media server to identify your browser whenever you interact with the ADS Live Media site or with an ADS Live Media Publisher site. ADS Live Media uses cookies to recognize repeat visits by users of its Service and to collect information about its users’ interactions with the Services. These cookies contain identification information that enables us to streamline a user’s experiences using the Services and to report such information to Publishers, Advertisers, and Network Operators. You may set your browser software to reject cookies, but you may not be able to optimize the features of the Services. In some cases, you may not be able to access Services if cookies are disabled.

C. USE AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience.

1) If you are a Publisher we may share information about your site, including but not limited to page impressions, site traffic, prices and readership with Advertisers, Publishers, Network Operators. We will not share personally identifiable information about you with Advertisers without your prior written or electronic consent.

2) If you are an Advertiser we may disclose your contact information and email address to Publishers on whose Sites you have placed advertisements.

3) If you are a Publisher we may disclose your contact information and email address to Network Operators managing Networks that sell advertising on your behalf.

4) Disclosure for Marketing Purposes. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent.

5) Other Disclosures. ADS Live Media may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or if ADS Live Media has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to protect and/or defend the rights and interests of ADS Live Media. ADS Live Media may, as permitted by applicable law, disclose your personally identifiable information to Publishers, Advertisers, Network Operators, or third parties in connection with an investigation of fraud, infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity and you expressly authorize ADS Live Media to make such disclosures.

6) Contractors and Vendors. We use contractors and vendors, including information processing companies, to help with some of our operations. Some of these contractors will have access to our databases of Publisher, Advertiser, and Network Operator information on a temporary basis for specific tasks. ADS Live Media also uses vendors to help with certain aspects of its operations, which may require disclosure of your User Information to them. ADS Live Media contractually binds these contractors and vendors to use such information only as necessary to perform the services they are asked to perform.

7) Domestic and International Use. All personally identifying information collected by ADS Live Media may be used in the United States or, if the Service are undertaken by ADS Live Media for a non-US Publisher, Advertiser, or Network Operator, such information may be transferred to that Publisher, Advertiser, or Network Operator, outside of the United States, and through your use of the Service you hereby consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

8) Merger or Acquisition. If ADS Live Media is merged or acquired by another entity, personally identifiable information may be transferred to such entity as a part of the merger or acquisition.

9) Factors Beyond Our Control. Your privacy is very important to us. Due to factors beyond our control, however, we cannot fully ensure that your personal information will not be disclosed to third parties. For example, we may be legally obligated to disclose such information to local, state or federal governmental agencies or other third parties under certain circumstances (including in response to a subpoena), or third parties may circumvent our security measures to unlawfully intercept or access your personal information.

D. LINKS TO OTHER SITES

As a part of the Service, ADS Live Media provides links to sites operated by third parties. ADS Live Media is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices or the content of those third party sites.

E. DELETE COOKIES

Google Chrome

Click on the “Tools” menu and select “Options”.  
Click the “Under the Bonnet” tab, locate the “Privacy” section and click the “Clear browsing data” button.  
Select “Delete cookies and other site data” to delete all cookies from the list (alternatively, you can remove all cookies created within a specific time period by selecting the period you want from the dropdown list).  
Select “Clear browsing history” to delete traces of which websites you’ve visited.  
Select “Clear download history” to delete records of which files and programs you’ve downloaded.  
Select “Empty the cache” to delete cached website pages.  
You can also delete saved passwords (which log you into websites) and saved form data (such as your name and address).  
Then click on the “Clear browsing data” button.  
Click on the Close button when you’ve finished.  
Internet Explorer 9

Open Internet explorer window  
Click the “Tools” button  
Point to “safety” and then click “delete browsing history”  
Tick the “cookies” box, then click “delete”  
AOL 8 and 9

Sign on and select Settings from the toolbar.  
Version 9.0 users should select the By Category tab and click the Internet [Web] Options link, while for Version 8.0 and below click Internet Properties (WWW).  
Click Settings.  
Note: Windows Vista will see more than one Settings button. Click the button in the Browsing history section.  
Click View Files. Your list of cookies (plus your other temporary internet files) will be displayed.  
If you wish to delete any of the cookies or files, right-click on them and choose Delete.  
Mozilla Firefox

Click on Tools, then Options (or Edit | Preferences on Linux)  
Select Privacy  
In the Cookies panel, click on Show Cookies  
To remove a single cookie click on the entry in the list and click on the Remove Cookie button  
To remove all cookies click on the Remove All Cookies button  
Netscape Navigator 7.x

Choose Cookie Manager from the Tools menu.  
Choose Manage Stored Cookies.  
Remove any cookie from the list, or remove all cookies.  
Opera

To delete all cookies at the end of every session, select it in the privacy settings under Tools > Preferences.  
Click on Manage cookies to delete specific cookies or cookies from specific domains  
To delete all cookies immediately, go to Delete private data on the Tools menu.  
OpenX Cookie Opt-Out

http://www.openx.com/about/privacy-policy

F. INFORMATION SECURITY

ADS Live Media uses commercially reasonable efforts to store personally identifiable information obtained through registration securely and considers it part of the assets of its business. All information is stored in our servers located inside the United States. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain accuracy of information, and ensure the appropriate use of information, ADS Live Media has put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information it collects online. However, information security is a constantly evolving art and science, and no information is completely secure.

Your password is the key to your ADS Live Media account. Use unique numbers, letters, and special characters, and do not disclose your ADS Live Media password to anyone, even an ADS Live Media representative. If you do share your password or your personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify ADS Live Media and change your password.

G. FURTHER INFORMATION

If you have any questions about anything in this Privacy Policy, or about collection of personally identifiable information, or information generally, please contact ADS Live Media via info@adslivemedia.com.

H. ENTIRE AGREEMENT

The term “including” in this Privacy Policy shall mean “including without limitation.” This Privacy Policy supplements and is incorporated into the Network Operator Agreement (if applicable) and the Terms and Conditions. This Privacy Policy constitutes the entire agreement, and replaces and supersedes all prior agreements, between you and ADS Live Media concerning the subject matter discussed in this Privacy Policy. Access to your account will signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

BY USING THE ADS LIVE MEDIA SERVICE, I REPRESENT THAT I HAVE READ AND UNDERSTOOD THIS ENTIRE PRIVACY POLICY AND I AGREE TO ALL THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AS STATED ABOVE.
